[
    {
        "front": "はたらきます",
        "back": "To work",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "べんきょう します",
        "back": "To study",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "おわります",
        "back": "To finish",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "まいあさ",
        "back": "Every morning",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "まいばん",
        "back": "Every Evening",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "まいにち",
        "back": "Everyday",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "やすみ",
        "back": "Holiday, Break",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひるやすみ",
        "back": "Lunch break",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "やすみます",
        "back": "To take a break",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "えき",
        "back": "Station",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんしゃ",
        "back": "Train",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひこうき",
        "back": "Aeroplane",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふね",
        "back": "Ship, boat",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふつう",
        "back": "Local (train)",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいそく",
        "back": "Rapid (train)",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんかいそく",
        "back": "Special rapid (train)",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんかんせん",
        "back": "Bullet Train",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "じてんしゃ",
        "back": "Bycycle",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "かれ",
        "back": "He, Boyfriend",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "かのじょ",
        "back": "She, Girlfriend",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "かぞく",
        "back": "Family",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "せんげつ",
        "back": "Last month",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんげつ",
        "back": "This month",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいげつ",
        "back": "Next month",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょねん",
        "back": "Last year",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "ことし",
        "back": "This year",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "らいねん",
        "back": "Next year",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "もう",
        "back": "Already",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "にぎやか",
        "back": "Lively",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうしつ",
        "back": "Classroom",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんたん",
        "back": "Simple",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんき",
        "back": "Weather",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "あめ",
        "back": "Rain",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちばん",
        "back": "most-",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "はじめて",
        "back": "For the first time",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "1ねん",
        "back": "1 year",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "あまり",
        "back": "Not that much",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "おとこ",
        "back": "Male",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "おっな",
        "back": "Female",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "IMC",
        "back": "Name of company",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "この ちかく",
        "back": "Near this area",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "にわ",
        "back": "Garden",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうびんきょく",
        "back": "Post office",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "まえ",
        "back": "in front of",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "ざぶとん",
        "back": "Sitting Cushion",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうめい",
        "back": "Proof",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "かしこい",
        "back": "Smart",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "うた",
        "back": "Sing",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "はこ",
        "back": "Box",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "てがみ",
        "back": "Letter",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    },
    {
        "front": "きせつ",
        "back": "Season",
        "chapter": "N5 C9"
    }
]